Office of Student Services, School of Dental Medicine Records UA235
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Office of Student Services, School of Dental Medicine Records
1948 -- 2018
1991 -- 2018
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
School of Dental Medicine
UA235
142.1 Linear Feet 119 boxes
Conditions Governing Access
Records containing information related to student education, staff and faculty employment, and Board of Trustees records are closed for 75 years from the date of creation.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transferred by the Office of Student Services, School of Dental Medicine, 2014-2020.
Arrangement
This collection is organized into five series: Student records; Post graduate files; Grade sheets; Withdrawn or Dismissed students; 2016 accessions; and Unprocessed accessions.
Biographical / Historical
Tufts University School of Dental Medicine was established in 1868 as Boston Dental College. It was incorporated into Tufts College in 1899. Although founded as a school to educate students from New England, today Tufts is renowned throughout the United States and the world as a center for academic and clinical excellence. Tufts boasts over 6,900 alumni composed of individuals from all fifty states and thirty-nine countries. The majority of the alumni outside of the USA have completed an Advanced Education Certificate program. Students receive a comprehensive education emphasizing the importance of didactic coursework, clinical experience, and practice management that prepares them to enter the work force as confident, proficient clinicians.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains transcripts and other student records generated or received by the School of Dental Medicine, including administrative clearance forms for graduation; admission letters, applications, and recommendations; correspondence, financial records; and grade sheets. The bulk of the material is dated from 1991 to 2015.
Student Affairs and Services
- Student Records, 1998 -- 2018; UA235.001; 74.4 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains Doctor of Dental Medicine student records. Types of records found in these files include transcripts of Dental School and undergraduate institutions, admission letters and recommendations, applications, evaluations, photographs, and other personal information. The year listed for each student is the date of their graduation. If student was an international student, it is noted in the description.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically by graduation year and alphabetically within each year, where possible.
  Conditions Governing Access
  75 years from the date of creation.
  - Adler, Eric S, 2001; UA235.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - Antun, Reem, 2001; UA235.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - Apergis, Maria D, 2001; UA235.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - Armaleh, Mirna T, 2001; UA235.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
  - Atighechi, Sharok, 2001; UA235.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - Azenheimer, David R, 2000; UA235.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - Baloul, Soulafa S, 2001; UA235.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
  - Berty, Pascale E, 2000; UA235.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - Berube, Carrie R, 2001; UA235.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - Bock, Jakob C, 2001; UA235.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
  - Brooks, Michael D, 2001; UA235.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
  - Buitrago-Defabrique, Angela, 2001; UA235.001.001.00012 (Box 1)
  - Chan, Nathaniel, 2001; UA235.001.001.00013 (Box 1)
  - Chen, Shih-Yao, 2001; UA235.001.001.00014 (Box 1)
  - Cho, Ian I, 2001; UA235.001.001.00015 (Box 1)
  - Choe, Seong O, 2001; UA235.001.001.00016 (Box 1)
  - Clancy, Anne-Marie, 2001; UA235.001.001.00017 (Box 1)
  - Clancy, Ryan M, 2001; UA235.001.001.00018 (Box 1)
  - Curtis, Jason A, 2000; UA235.001.001.00019 (Box 1)
  - Dasoki, Ahmad K, 2000; UA235.001.001.00020 (Box 1)
  - Diaz, Nelson J, 2001; UA235.001.001.00021 (Box 1)
  - Do, Yongsok, 2001; UA235.001.001.00022 (Box 1)
  - Duong, Derek Q, 2001; UA235.001.001.00023 (Box 1)
  - Ellis, Scott B, 2001; UA235.001.001.00024 (Box 1)
  - Fay, Terese N, 2001; UA235.001.001.00025 (Box 1)
  - Ferro, David D, 2001; UA235.001.001.00026 (Box 1)
  - Foglia, Michele L, 2001; UA235.001.001.00027 (Box 1)
  - Ghodsi, Shayan, 2001; UA235.001.001.00028 (Box 1)
  - Golara, Elika, 2001; UA235.001.001.00029 (Box 1)
  - Grilli, Gary F, 2001; UA235.001.001.00030 (Box 1)
  - Grosman, Alon, 2001; UA235.001.001.00031 (Box 1)
  - Hallisey, Karen D, 2001; UA235.001.001.00032 (Box 1)
  - Hameed, Kamran, 2001; UA235.001.001.00033 (Box 1)
  - Hegazi, Mohamed A, 2001; UA235.001.001.00034 (Box 1)
  - Hong, Seungchul, 2001; UA235.001.001.00035 (Box 1)
  - Hoye, Erin K, 2001; UA235.001.001.00036 (Box 1)
  - Hutchinson, Paul G, 2001; UA235.001.001.00037 (Box 1)
  - Jackson, Terence S, 2001; UA235.001.001.00038 (Box 1)
  - Jafferally, Akbar H, 2001; UA235.001.001.00039 (Box 1)
  - Kae, Joon W, 2001; UA235.001.001.00040 (Box 1)
  - Kalavrouzoitis, Efthimios, 2001; UA235.001.001.00041 (Box 1)
  - Kanchanlal, Viklash, 2001; UA235.001.001.00042 (Box 1)
  - Kang, Paul Sangwon, 2001; UA235.001.002.00001 (Box 2)
  - Kim, Dong S., 2001; UA235.001.002.00002 (Box 2)
  - Kim, Gun-nam, 2001; UA235.001.002.00003 (Box 2)
  - Kim, Mee-yung, 2001; UA235.001.002.00004 (Box 2)
  - Kitchens, Heather L., 2001; UA235.001.002.00005 (Box 2)
  - Kmet, Sandra A., 2001; UA235.001.002.00006 (Box 2)
  - Ko, Wing H., 2001; UA235.001.002.00007 (Box 2)
  - Kurtz, Renee L., 2001; UA235.001.002.00008 (Box 2)
  - Lalsingh, Chad K., 2001; UA235.001.002.00009 (Box 2)
  - Lee, Hyun-Sook, 2001; UA235.001.002.00010 (Box 2)
  - Lee, Jin-Ho, 2001; UA235.001.002.00011 (Box 2)
  - Lee, John H., 2001; UA235.001.002.00012 (Box 2)
  - Leland, Robert S., 2001; UA235.001.002.00013 (Box 2)
  - Lemieux, Henry E., 2001; UA235.001.002.00014 (Box 2)
  - Liakos, Despina, 2001; UA235.001.002.00015 (Box 2)
  - Livshin, Ilya A., 2001; UA235.001.002.00016 (Box 2)
  - Livshin, Svetlana, 2001; UA235.001.002.00017 (Box 2)
  - Lloyd, Ryan R., 2001; UA235.001.002.00018 (Box 2)
  - Luu, Tram B., 2001; UA235.001.002.00019 (Box 2)
  - MacDonald, Stuart J., 2001; UA235.001.002.00020 (Box 2)
  - Malecki, Magdalena Z., 2001; UA235.001.002.00021 (Box 2)
  - Mancuso, Matthew D., 2001; UA235.001.002.00022 (Box 2)
  - Marciniszyn, Katherine, 2001; UA235.001.002.00023 (Box 2)
  - Martin, Stephen R., 2001; UA235.001.002.00024 (Box 2)
  - Masterson, Thomas E., 2001; UA235.001.002.00025 (Box 2)
  - Mazzoccoli, Lisa S., 2001; UA235.001.002.00026 (Box 2)
  - Mercier, Michelle K., 2001; UA235.001.002.00027 (Box 2)
  - Meshkati, Katherine S., 2001; UA235.001.002.00028 (Box 2)
  - Migadakis, Evanthia, 2001; UA235.001.002.00029 (Box 2)
  - Millett, Brian S., 2001; UA235.001.002.00030 (Box 2)
  - Moghaddam, Nina T., 2001; UA235.001.002.00031 (Box 2)
  - Moore, Jennifer A., 2001; UA235.001.002.00032 (Box 2)
  - Morgan, Sheree, 2001; UA235.001.002.00033 (Box 2)
  - Moynihan, Robert B., 2001; UA235.001.002.00034 (Box 2)
  - Nahata, Nitish, 2001; UA235.001.002.00035 (Box 2)
  - Najaran, Sepideh, 2001; UA235.001.002.00036 (Box 2)
  - Naujoks, Andrea D., 2001; UA235.001.002.00037 (Box 2)
  - Naumovski, Fanche M., 2001; UA235.001.002.00038 (Box 2)
  - Nguyen, Huan, 2001; UA235.001.002.00039 (Box 2)
  - Nguyen, Trang T, 2001; UA235.001.002.00040 (Box 2)
  - Nguyen, Yen T., 2001; UA235.001.002.00041 (Box 2)
  - Oles Karasko, Anita S., 2001; UA235.001.002.00042 (Box 2)
  - Nghiem, Bruce M., 2001; UA235.001.002.00043 (Box 2)
  - Oong, Ella M, 2001; UA235.001.003.00001 (Box 3)
  - Patel, Amit V, 2001; UA235.001.003.00002 (Box 3)
  - Patel, Apurva A, 2001; UA235.001.003.00003 (Box 3)
  - Patsi, Vasiliki, 2001; UA235.001.003.00004 (Box 3)
  - Pfister, Candace K, 2000; UA235.001.003.00005 (Box 3)
  - Phan, Sandy N, 2001; UA235.001.003.00006 (Box 3)
  - Pollack, Ginger M, 2000; UA235.001.003.00007 (Box 3)
  - Pourati, Jacob A, 2000; UA235.001.003.00008 (Box 3)
  - Prilutsky, Yigal, 2001; UA235.001.003.00009 (Box 3)
  - Quasha, Michael D, 2001; UA235.001.003.00010 (Box 3)
  - Raeisian, Nazinin N, 2001; UA235.001.003.00011 (Box 3)
  - Raisman, Stephen S, 2001; UA235.001.003.00012 (Box 3)
  - Rand, Katie M, 2001; UA235.001.003.00013 (Box 3)
  - Ranta, Jeffrey A, 1999; UA235.001.003.00014 (Box 3)
  - Reidy, Joseph A, 2001; UA235.001.003.00015 (Box 3)
  - Reposa, Ryan D, 2001; UA235.001.003.00016 (Box 3)
  - Rhim, Catherine S, 2001; UA235.001.003.00017 (Box 3)
  - Rollins, S. Andre, 2001; UA235.001.003.00018 (Box 3)
  - Rose, Scott P, 2001; UA235.001.003.00019 (Box 3)
  - Russo, Gregory A, 2001; UA235.001.003.00020 (Box 3)
  - Saati, Mona, 2001; UA235.001.003.00021 (Box 3)
  - Safarian, Shahin, 2001; UA235.001.003.00022 (Box 3)
  - Salibian, David, 2000; UA235.001.003.00023 (Box 3)
  - Saraydarian, John G, 2001; UA235.001.003.00024 (Box 3)
  - Shick, Paul K, 2001; UA235.001.003.00025 (Box 3)
  - Spagnuolo, Christina E, 2001; UA235.001.003.00026 (Box 3)
  - Stanton, Robert, 2001; UA235.001.003.00027 (Box 3)
  - Stern, Karyn L, 2001; UA235.001.003.00028 (Box 3)
  - Swensen, Lars, 2001; UA235.001.003.00029 (Box 3)
  - Son, Misuk, 2001; UA235.001.003.00030 (Box 3)
  - Song, Jae-Yun, 2000; UA235.001.003.00031 (Box 3)
  - Shusterman, Jon D, 2001; UA235.001.003.00032 (Box 3)
  - Sidhu, Jessy S, 2000; UA235.001.003.00033 (Box 3)
  - Silvia, James E, 2001; UA235.001.003.00034 (Box 3)
  - Smith, Craig E., 2001; UA235.001.003.00035 (Box 3)
  - Tabatabaie, Rozita E, 2001; UA235.001.003.00036 (Box 3)
  - Ting, Brian L, 2001; UA235.001.003.00037 (Box 3)
  - Tran, Lan T, 2001; UA235.001.003.00038 (Box 3)
  - Trnovsky, Jana, 2001; UA235.001.003.00039 (Box 3)
  - Truong, Hoang-Vu M, 2001; UA235.001.003.00040 (Box 3)
  - Vang, Kong, 2001; UA235.001.003.00041 (Box 3)
  - Vizentin, Elizabeth E, 2001; UA235.001.003.00042 (Box 3)
  - Abdullaibrahim, Abe, 2002; UA235.001.004.00001 (Box 4)
  - Adams, Shawna, 2002; UA235.001.004.00002 (Box 4)
  - Adeli-Nadjafi, Alireza, 2002; UA235.001.004.00003 (Box 4)
  - Ahmadzada, Zia, 2002; UA235.001.004.00004 (Box 4)
  - Anene, Christopher, 2002; UA235.001.004.00005 (Box 4)
  - Arango, Li, 2002; UA235.001.004.00006 (Box 4)
  - Avila, Eduardo A, 2002; UA235.001.004.00007 (Box 4)
  - Baloul, Kamar M, 2002; UA235.001.004.00008 (Box 4)
  - Bamdad, Navid, 2002; UA235.001.004.00009 (Box 4)
  - Banahatti, Priya, 2002; UA235.001.004.00010 (Box 4)
  - Barnard, Julia A, 2002; UA235.001.004.00011 (Box 4)
  - Barzi, Glorya, 2002; UA235.001.004.00012 (Box 4)
  - Batchelder, Karen M, 2002; UA235.001.004.00013 (Box 4)
  - Baumgardner, Thomas R, 2002; UA235.001.004.00014 (Box 4)
  - Bedi, Abhayjit S, 2002; UA235.001.004.00015 (Box 4)
  - Bingham, Vickii R, 2002; UA235.001.004.00016 (Box 4)
  - Bjornson, Thomas G, 2002; UA235.001.004.00017 (Box 4)
  - Blain, Carla M, 2002; UA235.001.004.00018 (Box 4)
  - Boehm, Michael E, 2002; UA235.001.004.00019 (Box 4)
  - Bradford, Blair A, 2002; UA235.001.004.00020 (Box 4)
  - Brody, Amanda R, 2002; UA235.001.004.00021 (Box 4)
  - Bruney, Keisha P, 2002; UA235.001.004.00022 (Box 4)
  - Burns, Kendall R, 2002; UA235.001.004.00023 (Box 4)
  - Butkevich, Ekaterina E, 2002; UA235.001.004.00024 (Box 4)
  - Calderon, Alfredo J, 2002; UA235.001.004.00025 (Box 4)
  - Capretta, Nina, 2002; UA235.001.004.00026 (Box 4)
  - Castaneda, Ricardo, 2002; UA235.001.004.00027 (Box 4)
  - Chahal, Manpreet, 2002; UA235.001.004.00028 (Box 4)
  - Cheema, Sandeep S, 2002; UA235.001.004.00029 (Box 4)
  - Chen, Fang, 2002; UA235.001.004.00030 (Box 4)
  - Cho, Christian E, 2002; UA235.001.004.00031 (Box 4)
  - Choe, Kristen J, 2002; UA235.001.004.00032 (Box 4)
  - Choi, Daniel H, 2002; UA235.001.004.00033 (Box 4)
  - Choi, Samuel, 2002; UA235.001.004.00034 (Box 4)
  - Ciccone, Richard, 2002; UA235.001.004.00035 (Box 4)
  - Coleman, Cara A, 2002; UA235.001.004.00036 (Box 4)
  - Creech, Hadley A, 2002; UA235.001.004.00037 (Box 4)
  - Crowley, Sandra J, 2002; UA235.001.004.00038 (Box 4)
  - Dickinson, Grace G, 2002; UA235.001.004.00039 (Box 4)
  - Dionisopoulos, Fotini M., 2002; UA235.001.005.00001 (Box 5)
  - Dong, Michael C., 2002; UA235.001.005.00002 (Box 5)
  - Dunn, Katherine A., 2002; UA235.001.005.00003 (Box 5)
  - Eberhardt, Alan C., 2002; UA235.001.005.00004 (Box 5)
  - Feeney, John J., 2002; UA235.001.005.00005 (Box 5)
  - Ferreira, Michael D., 2002; UA235.001.005.00006 (Box 5)
  - Gamber, Paul S., 2002; UA235.001.005.00007 (Box 5)
  - Ghent, Gretchen A., 2002; UA235.001.005.00008 (Box 5)
  - Ginsburg, Matthew S., 2002; UA235.001.005.00009 (Box 5)
  - Godley, Mary F., 2002; UA235.001.005.00010 (Box 5)
  - Goldstein, Leigh R., 2002; UA235.001.005.00011 (Box 5)
  - Gould, Jason M., 2002; UA235.001.005.00012 (Box 5)
  - Gray, Jeffrey F., 2002; UA235.001.005.00013 (Box 5)
  - Greenwood, Wayne A., 2002; UA235.001.005.00014 (Box 5)
  - Gutnichenko, Y., 2002; UA235.001.005.00015; International Student (Box 5)
  - Haghavegh, Shahrzad, 2002; UA235.001.005.00016 (Box 5)
  - Hakimi, Vigal S., 2002; UA235.001.005.00017 (Box 5)
  - Heil, Edgar A., 2002; UA235.001.005.00018 (Box 5)
  - Henderson, Jason D., 2002; UA235.001.005.00019 (Box 5)
  - Homer, Michael D., 2002; UA235.001.005.00020 (Box 5)
  - Jajou, Nazih, 2002; UA235.001.005.00021; International Student (Box 5)
  - Jih, Joshua M., 2002; UA235.001.005.00022 (Box 5)
  - Joo, Carlos G., 2002; UA235.001.005.00023 (Box 5)
  - Jorden, Monserrat, 2002; UA235.001.005.00024; International Student (Box 5)
  - Kalinian, Susan S., 2002; UA235.001.005.00025 (Box 5)
  - Kalmanovich, Anna Y., 2002; UA235.001.005.00026; International Student (Box 5)
  - Karogiannis, Angela, 2002; UA235.001.005.00027 (Box 5)
  - Kennon, Ann T., 2002; UA235.001.005.00028 (Box 5)
  - Khrustcheva, Natalia N., 2002; UA235.001.005.00029 (Box 5)
  - Kim, Kyung S., 2002; UA235.001.005.00030 (Box 5)
  - King, Samantha D., 2002; UA235.001.005.00031 (Box 5)
  - Koehler, Rebecca A., 2002; UA235.001.005.00032 (Box 5)
  - Koo, Grace H., 2002; UA235.001.005.00033 (Box 5)
  - Kothari, Reema, 2002; UA235.001.005.00034; International Student (Box 5)
  - Krajekian, Joseph, 2002; UA235.001.005.00035 (Box 5)
  - Krasyuk, Zhana V., 2002; UA235.001.005.00036 (Box 5)
  - Labombard, Brian E., 2002; UA235.001.005.00037 (Box 5)
  - Larsen, Joseph M., 2002; UA235.001.005.00038 (Box 5)
  - Latypova, Kateryna, 2002; UA235.001.005.00039; International Student (Box 5)
  - Lauretano, Ralph J., 2002; UA235.001.005.00040 (Box 5)
  - Lauritzen, Cliff N., 2002; UA235.001.005.00041 (Box 5)
  - Lee, Norman E., 2002; UA235.001.005.00042 (Box 5)
  - Lee, Yu-Jin, 2002; UA235.001.005.00043 (Box 5)
  - Lerman, Mark A., 2002; UA235.001.005.00044 (Box 5)
  - Lieu, Yen N, 2002; UA235.001.006.00001 (Box 6)
  - Lim, Sum-Eun S, 2002; UA235.001.006.00002 (Box 6)
  - Lopez, Kerri L, 2002; UA235.001.006.00003 (Box 6)
  - Lucca Jr, Donald A, 2002; UA235.001.006.00004 (Box 6)
  - Lung, Mariela K, 2002; UA235.001.006.00005 (Box 6)
  - Maguire, Brian T, 2002; UA235.001.006.00006 (Box 6)
  - Mandel, Dana L, 2002; UA235.001.006.00007 (Box 6)
  - Mantzikos, Katherine, 2002; UA235.001.006.00008 (Box 6)
  - Melnick, Dania, 2002; UA235.001.006.00009 (Box 6)
  - Merchant, Fahra H, 2002; UA235.001.006.00010 (Box 6)
  - Min, Michael J, 2002; UA235.001.006.00011 (Box 6)
  - Molime, Stanislav A, 2002; UA235.001.006.00012 (Box 6)
  - Moro, Roberta A, 2002; UA235.001.006.00013 (Box 6)
  - Moshirfar, Catherine J, 2002; UA235.001.006.00014 (Box 6)
  - Mull, Justin C, 2002; UA235.001.006.00015 (Box 6)
  - Naidu, Kistama, 2002; UA235.001.006.00016 (Box 6)
  - Narayanan, Neeraja, 2002; UA235.001.006.00017 (Box 6)
  - Nedwetzky, Danielle, 2002; UA235.001.006.00018 (Box 6)
  - Newcomb, Jonathan C, 2002; UA235.001.006.00019 (Box 6)
  - Nguyen, Christina, 2002; UA235.001.006.00020 (Box 6)
  - Nguyen, Kari A, 2002; UA235.001.006.00021 (Box 6)
  - Nguyen, Henry, 2002; UA235.001.006.00022 (Box 6)
  - Nguyen, Minh T, 2002; UA235.001.006.00023 (Box 6)
  - Nguyen, Thuy Phuong B, 2002; UA235.001.006.00024 (Box 6)
  - Niaraki, Mayson A, 2002; UA235.001.006.00025 (Box 6)
  - Osinovskaya, Renata, 2002; UA235.001.006.00026 (Box 6)
  - Padron, Aida, 2002; UA235.001.006.00027 (Box 6)
  - Park, Jihyun, 2002; UA235.001.006.00028 (Box 6)
  - Park, Yeun-June, 2002; UA235.001.006.00029 (Box 6)
  - Parradee, Randy S, 2002; UA235.001.006.00030 (Box 6)
  - Parris, Christopher K, 2002; UA235.001.006.00031 (Box 6)
  - Perrinsky, Victoria, 2002; UA235.001.006.00032 (Box 6)
  - Pfeifer, Errin J, 2002; UA235.001.006.00033 (Box 6)
  - Price, Richard M, 2002; UA235.001.006.00034 (Box 6)
  - Priftakis, Stephen L, 2002; UA235.001.006.00035 (Box 6)
  - Reddy, Vidya, 2002; UA235.001.006.00036 (Box 6)
  - Rodgers, Melissa W, 2002; UA235.001.006.00037 (Box 6)
  - Roh, Yoonchul, 2002; UA235.001.006.00038 (Box 6)
  - Rohany, Tania, 2002; UA235.001.006.00039 (Box 6)
  - Rojas, Tamara, 2002; UA235.001.006.00040 (Box 6)
  - Romano, Mark A, 2002; UA235.001.006.00041 (Box 6)
  - Ross, Ben B, 2002; UA235.001.006.00042 (Box 6)
  - Scull, Paul J, 2002; UA235.001.007.00001 (Box 7)
  - Shafiei, Padideh, 2002; UA235.001.007.00002 (Box 7)
  - Sharma, Meenakshi, 2002; UA235.001.007.00003 (Box 7)
  - Sharp, Debra J, 2002; UA235.001.007.00004 (Box 7)
  - Sim, Jung, 2002; UA235.001.007.00005 (Box 7)
  - Singh, Charanpreet, 2002; UA235.001.007.00006 (Box 7)
  - Smith, Andrew M, 2002; UA235.001.007.00007 (Box 7)
  - Snigger, Lisa A, 2002; UA235.001.007.00008 (Box 7)
  - Soden, Ryan, 2002; UA235.001.007.00009 (Box 7)
  - Tarshis, Carrie A, 2002; UA235.001.007.00010 (Box 7)
  - Thatcher, Dawn A, 2002; UA235.001.007.00011 (Box 7)
  - Thompson, Glenn D, 2002; UA235.001.007.00012 (Box 7)
  - Thomson, Scott E, 2002; UA235.001.007.00013 (Box 7)
  - Truong, Minhchau V, 2002; UA235.001.007.00014 (Box 7)
  - Vo, Hung Q, 2002; UA235.001.007.00015 (Box 7)
  - Vu, Gwendolyn T, 2002; UA235.001.007.00016 (Box 7)
  - Vuong, Phuoc T, 2002; UA235.001.007.00017 (Box 7)
  - Walji, Farah, 2002; UA235.001.007.00018 (Box 7)
  - Wang, Lei, 2002; UA235.001.007.00019 (Box 7)
  - Wang, Xin, 2002; UA235.001.007.00020 (Box 7)
  - Wetherhold, Joseph H, 2002; UA235.001.007.00021 (Box 7)
  - Wilson, Patrick T, 2002; UA235.001.007.00022 (Box 7)
  - Winstead, Nadia A, 2002; UA235.001.007.00023 (Box 7)
  - Won, Bo-Young, 2002; UA235.001.007.00024 (Box 7)
  - Yi, Jihae I, 2002; UA235.001.007.00025 (Box 7)
  - Youssef, Marianne, 2002; UA235.001.007.00026 (Box 7)
  - Yu, Janet K, 2002; UA235.001.007.00027 (Box 7)
  - Yuan, Monique, 2002; UA235.001.007.00028 (Box 7)
  - Yuan, Robert S, 2002; UA235.001.007.00029 (Box 7)
  - Zemnick, Candice B, 2002; UA235.001.007.00030 (Box 7)
  - Zhang, Li, 2002; UA235.001.007.00031 (Box 7)
  - Zhang, Yi, 2002; UA235.001.007.00032 (Box 7)
  - Outericka, Edita, 2002; UA235.001.007.00033 (Box 7)
  - Lucca, Mario G, 2002; UA235.001.007.00034 (Box 7)
  - Davuluri, Ameena, 2002; UA235.001.007.00035 (Box 7)
  - Kolli Bindu, 2002; UA235.001.007.00036 (Box 7)
  - Yu Sheng H., 2002; UA235.001.007.00037 (Box 7)
  - Abudu, Madeline A, 2003; UA235.001.008.00001 (Box 8)
  - Mati, Suhail, 2003; UA235.001.008.00002 (Box 8)
  - Alonso Jr, Anthony, 2003; UA235.001.008.00003 (Box 8)
  - Ancich, Nicole M, 2003; UA235.001.008.00004 (Box 8)
  - Arora-Mohan, Tina, 2003; UA235.001.008.00005 (Box 8)
  - Athanasiou, Alexander, 2003; UA235.001.008.00006 (Box 8)
  - Au-Yeung, David, 2003; UA235.001.008.00007 (Box 8)
  - Avvaru, Sreelatha, 2003; UA235.001.008.00008 (Box 8)
  - Baek, Woo J, 2003; UA235.001.008.00009 (Box 8)
  - Bartek, Gregory M, 2003; UA235.001.008.00010 (Box 8)
  - Beasley, Julie S, 2003; UA235.001.008.00011 (Box 8)
  - Berg, Robert W, 2003; UA235.001.008.00012 (Box 8)
  - Bertetti, Richard D, 2003; UA235.001.008.00013 (Box 8)
  - Bhagchandani, Sanjay P, 2003; UA235.001.008.00014 (Box 8)
  - Blandon, Guillermina M, 2003; UA235.001.008.00015 (Box 8)
  - Bock, Derek J, 2003; UA235.001.008.00016 (Box 8)
  - Brown, Laurie M, 2003; UA235.001.008.00017 (Box 8)
  - Brusseau, Eileen C, 2003; UA235.001.008.00018 (Box 8)
  - Bui, Kenneth Q, 2003; UA235.001.008.00019 (Box 8)
  - Cardone, Anthony A, 2003; UA235.001.008.00020 (Box 8)
  - Cerqueira, Paula C, 2003; UA235.001.008.00021 (Box 8)
  - Chen, Wei P, 2003; UA235.001.008.00022 (Box 8)
  - Choi, John J, 2003; UA235.001.008.00023 (Box 8)
  - Chu, Joannie, 2003; UA235.001.008.00024 (Box 8)
  - Courtman, Jessica T, 2003; UA235.001.008.00025 (Box 8)
  - Creamer, Wesley S, 2003; UA235.001.008.00026 (Box 8)
  - Crispin, Kristi A, 2003; UA235.001.008.00027 (Box 8)
  - Crowley, Paul C, 2003; UA235.001.008.00028 (Box 8)
  - Cruz, Ethel S, 2003; UA235.001.008.00029 (Box 8)
  - Daci, Ina, 2003; UA235.001.008.00030 (Box 8)
  - Dalia, Anokhi D, 2003; UA235.001.008.00031 (Box 8)
  - Davenport, Jaime S, 2003; UA235.001.008.00032 (Box 8)
  - Dexter, Jefferson S, 2003; UA235.001.008.00033 (Box 8)
  - Perera, Volani, 2003; UA235.001.008.00034 (Box 8)
  - Eftekhari, Tandis, 2003; UA235.001.008.00035 (Box 8)
  - Elgohary, Anthony A, 2003; UA235.001.008.00036 (Box 8)
  - Elseed, Mohammed A, 2003; UA235.001.008.00037 (Box 8)
  - Feist, Tricia S., 2003; UA235.001.008.00038 (Box 8)
  - Fox, Matthew Z, 2003; UA235.001.008.00039 (Box 8)
  - Freccero, Craig R, 2003; UA235.001.009.00001 (Box 9)
  - Geller, Brett M, 2003; UA235.001.009.00002 (Box 9)
  - Gerber, Jeremy, 2003; UA235.001.009.00003 (Box 9)
  - Gibbs, Jenel R, 2003; UA235.001.009.00004 (Box 9)
  - Gitlin, Galina, 2003; UA235.001.009.00005 (Box 9)
  - Hammer, Joshua D, 2003; UA235.001.009.00006 (Box 9)
  - Handwerk, Lauren E, 2003; UA235.001.009.00007 (Box 9)
  - Harde, Xandra L, 2003; UA235.001.009.00008 (Box 9)
  - Hassan, Siema, 2003; UA235.001.009.00009 (Box 9)
  - Hoye, Kathleen E, 2003; UA235.001.009.00010 (Box 9)
  - Huang, Grace W, 2003; UA235.001.009.00011 (Box 9)
  - Huang, James S, 2003; UA235.001.009.00012 (Box 9)
  - Jefferies, Mark S, 2003; UA235.001.009.00013 (Box 9)
  - Joseph, Michael, 2003; UA235.001.009.00014 (Box 9)
  - Judge, Jatinder, 2003; UA235.001.009.00015 (Box 9)
  - Kaleka, Ericdeep S, 2003; UA235.001.009.00016 (Box 9)
  - Kapoor, Nandita, 2003; UA235.001.009.00017 (Box 9)
  - Khodai, Shahbod, 2003; UA235.001.009.00018 (Box 9)
  - Kim, Minna S, 2003; UA235.001.009.00019 (Box 9)
  - Kim, Yongjeong, 2003; UA235.001.009.00020 (Box 9)
  - Koo, Vernon Y, 2003; UA235.001.009.00021 (Box 9)
  - Kostrov, Michael, 2003; UA235.001.009.00022 (Box 9)
  - Krause, Trisha A, 2003; UA235.001.009.00023 (Box 9)
  - Lacrampe, Etienne P, 2003; UA235.001.009.00024 (Box 9)
  - Lafauci, Richard D, 2003; UA235.001.009.00025 (Box 9)
  - Lam, Laura T, 2003; UA235.001.009.00026 (Box 9)
  - Lam, Timothy T, 2003; UA235.001.009.00027 (Box 9)
  - Ferriol, Maria C, 2003; UA235.001.009.00028 (Box 9)
  - Tran, Chi Q, 2003; UA235.001.009.00029 (Box 9)
  - Lee, Anthony C, 2003; UA235.001.009.00030 (Box 9)
  - Lee, Brian Y, 2003; UA235.001.009.00031 (Box 9)
  - Lee, Hyonchol, 2003; UA235.001.009.00032 (Box 9)
  - Lee, John S, 2003; UA235.001.009.00033 (Box 9)
  - Lee, Shandra C, 2003; UA235.001.009.00034 (Box 9)
  - Leong, Denise L, 2003; UA235.001.009.00035 (Box 9)
  - Lew, Edward W, 2003; UA235.001.009.00036 (Box 9)
  - Lin, Lennox, 2003; UA235.001.009.00037 (Box 9)
  - Lokko, Nii Norte, 2003; UA235.001.009.00038 (Box 9)
  - Loo, Kevin J, 2003; UA235.001.009.00039 (Box 9)
  - Lotfi, Pouyan, 2003; UA235.001.009.00040 (Box 9)
  - Lucier, Mark C, 2003; UA235.001.009.00041 (Box 9)
  - Lyn, Wayne S, 2003; UA235.001.009.00042 (Box 9)
  - Macallan, Iain David, 2003; UA235.001.010.00001 (Box 10)
  - Magnuson, Priscilla K, 2003; UA235.001.010.00002 (Box 10)
  - Mao, Chhy, 2003; UA235.001.010.00003 (Box 10)
  - Marcus, Gina R, 2003; UA235.001.010.00004 (Box 10)
  - Mashkouri, Nima, 2003; UA235.001.010.00005 (Box 10)
  - McGee, Matthew D, 2003; UA235.001.010.00006 (Box 10)
  - Mcgonigle, Christopher T, 2003; UA235.001.010.00007 (Box 10)
  - Mehanna, Rania S, 2003; UA235.001.010.00008 (Box 10)
  - Melbourne, Johl A, 2003; UA235.001.010.00009 (Box 10)
  - Merchant, Nadeem H, 2003; UA235.001.010.00010 (Box 10)